http://www.holocaust-trc.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
To improve our website
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
To improve customer service
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
To process transactions
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
Do we use cookies?
We do not use cookies.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Third Party Offerings
No products or services are sold by this website. Some books, videos, etc. are offered by third parties (e.g., Amazon and Social Studies School Service). Those transactions are governed solely by the policies and procedures of those third parties. In some instances, the Holocaust Education Foundation, Inc. receives a portion of the proceeds. Those funds are not an added cost to the purchaser.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.
This policy was last modified on March 1, 2013
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
This policy is powered by Free Privacy Policy and Rhino Support help desk software.
#6 (no title)
A Conspiracy of Indifference
A Global Perspective on Working with Holocaust Survivors and the Second Generation
Applying the Lessons of the Holocaust: from Particularism to Universalism and Back
Denying History: Who Says the Holocaust Never Happened and Why Do They Say It?
Divided Lives The Untold Stories of Jewish-Christian Women in Nazi Germany
Faith in God and Man After Auschwitz: Theological Implications
Hiding Places: A Father and His Sons Retrace Their Family’s Escape from the Holocaust
Humor in the Holocaust: Its Critical, Cohesive, and Coping Functions
In Sudan, Staring Genocide in the Face
Information Form
Intervision Volume No.1 Child Survivors: Forms of Intervention
Pack of Thieves: How Hitler and Europe Plundered the Jews and Committed the Greatest Theft in History
Persecution and Resistance of Jehovah’s Witnesses During the Nazi-Regime 1938-1945
Poles
Presentation to The Amsterdam Conference on Remembrance May 2001
Privacy Policy
Rekindling the Flame American Jewish Chaplains and the Survivors of European Jewry, 1944-1948
Spiritual, Educational, and Physical Resistance in the Warsaw Ghetto
The Man Who Stopped the Trains to Auschwitz George Mantello, El Salvador, and Switzerland’s Finest Hour
Where is God?
Teaching Empathy through Ecphrastic Poetry: Entering a Curriculum of Peace
Help support us by making a donation or a purchase through one of these sites.
Subscribe to our Mailing List
Sign Our Guestbook
Holocaust Teacher Resource Center © 2020  |  Privacy Policy | Site Map
#6 (no title)
A Conspiracy of Indifference
A Global Perspective on Working with Holocaust Survivors and the Second Generation
A Mother’s Shoah, The “Pessimists”
Applying the Lessons of the Holocaust: from Particularism to Universalism and Back
Dr. Shimon Samuels Video Clip
Book Reviews
Where is God?
Denying History: Who Says the Holocaust Never Happened and Why Do They Say It?
Divided Lives The Untold Stories of Jewish-Christian Women in Nazi Germany
Op-Ed: Lessons today from Sophie Scholl’s anti-Nazi resistance
Response to “Remembering the Holocaust’s 5 Million Others”
Reading Passages for slide (12)
Reading Passages for slides (13) and (14)
Questions for Discussion – slides (13) and (14)
Faith in God and Man After Auschwitz: Theological Implications
Hiding Places: A Father and His Sons Retrace Their Family’s Escape from the Holocaust
Students’ Worksheet — Questions Pertaining to the Historical Context of Each Responsum
Holocaust Wall Hangings
Homosexuals
Institute for Sexual Science
Paragraph 175
NAZI LEADER HEINRICH HIMMLER ON THE “QUESTION OF HOMOSEXUALITY”
A Homosexual Recalls 1933
Breaking the Silence: Friedrich-Paul Von Groszheim
Mugs
Humor in the Holocaust: Its Critical, Cohesive, and Coping Functions
In Sudan, Staring Genocide in the Face
Information Form
Intervision Volume No.1 Child Survivors: Forms of Intervention
Introduction
And Then, One Day … Whom Could I Tell?
Constant Agony*
Jehovah’s Witnesses
Mug shots of Jehovah’s Witnesses
Who Are Jehovah’s Witnesses?
Teaching the Holocaust: Light from the Yellow Star Leads the Way
Pack of Thieves: How Hitler and Europe Plundered the Jews and Committed the Greatest Theft in History
Persecution and Resistance of Jehovah’s Witnesses During the Nazi-Regime 1938-1945
Piesn Obozowa (Camp Song)
Presentation to The Amsterdam Conference on Remembrance May 2001
Professor Yehuda Bauer Video Clip
Privacy Policy
Rekindling the Flame American Jewish Chaplains and the Survivors of European Jewry, 1944-1948
Who Were the “Gypsies”?
Himmler’s Circular of December 8, 1938: “Combatting The Gypsy Nuisance”
Spiritual, Educational, and Physical Resistance in the Warsaw Ghetto
Why Teach Holocaust History?
Questions of Rationale
Methodological Considerations
Incorporating a Study of the Holocaust into Existing Courses
“Oh, No, It Can’t Be”
The Man Who Stopped the Trains to Auschwitz George Mantello, El Salvador, and Switzerland’s Finest Hour
Worksheet for Poster (11)
WORKSHEET FOR POSTER (13)
To Life
TO THE LITTLE POLISH BOY STANDING WITH HIS ARMS UP
TO THE LITTLE POLISH BOY STANDING WITH HIS ARMS UP, English Translation
TO THE LITTLE POLISH BOY STANDING WITH HIS ARMS UP, German Translation
Where is God?
Teaching Empathy through Ecphrastic Poetry: Entering a Curriculum of Peace
The Holocaust in Perspective
The Holocaust in Perspective Foreword to the Students
The Holocaust in Perspective Introduction
The Holocaust in Perspective, Chapter Analysis and Review
The Holocaust in Perspective, United States/Germany Comparison
The Holocaust in Perspective, Crime and Punishment: The Nuremberg Trials
The Holocaust in Perspective Teacher Manual
The Holocaust in Perspective Teacher Manual Forward to the Teachers
The Holocaust in Perspective Teacher Manual Course Objectives
The Holocaust in Perspective Teacher Manual Suggested Activities
The Holocaust in Perspective Teacher Manual A multi-disciplinary approach
